We're talking about yes, and and the idea of making offers, accepting offers, and building on those offers.
And I want to show you a game called yes, and brainstorm.
I like to do this game with a lot of my corporate clients.
It works well for businesses, meetings, organizations, anytime where people have to kind of create things together.
And how it works is you're going to get with your team, you can break up into groups of three, of four or five I think is a good size, it could go up to eight or ten.
And, what you're going to do is, is the team is going to have to come up with a new product and they're going to have to come up with an entire marketing plan for that product.
Come up with the packaging, the commercials, the jingle, the spokesperson, the billboards, you know, anything you can think of that would be part of the line of marketing.
What stores it might be in, what the slogan is going to be, and anything you can think of.
And they're going to have to do that as a group and they have to do it in three minutes.
And usually people at that point groan and go what are you talking about, that's impossible!
Well, it is possible with the magic of yes and.
So, we're going to show you how it's done.
We're going to do a yes, and marketing brainstorm.
I'm going to shout out my first idea, and Shannon is going to yes, and that idea.
He's going to say, yes, and, and then fill in the rest of his line, and we're going to go back and forth like that until we've got our product, all the product's features, its names, and the entire marketing plan.